{"question": ". M365 OS 11 // ? ( ) .xlsx (14 KB) =SUMIF(B3:B32,\"*\",D3:D32) =SUMIF(B3:B32,\"*\",D3:D32) 1 @ =SUMIF($B3 B32,\"*\",D3:D32) D33 =SUMIF($B3 B32,\"*\",D3:D32) D bona**** C33, →=SUM(FILTER(C5:C32,MOD(ROW(C5:C32)-2,3)=0))C35, X=BYCOL(C5:J32,LAMBDA(ErngCn, SUM(FILTER(ErngCn,MOD(ROW(ErngCn)-2,3)=0)))) C33, →=SUM(FILTER(C5:C32,MOD(ROW(C5:C32)-2,3)=0))C35, X=BYCOL(C5:J32,LAMBDA(ErngCn, SUM(FILTER(ErngCn,MOD(ROW(ErngCn)-2,3)=0)))) . TOP 1 / ... and IrOnWaRe foresth2u kimjin**** ! 1 QR ? cynicalH . () ? 2 & 2 1~13 ! GIA () hesed**** Power Pivot u**** ! 16 16 . mk**** 123...941", "answer": "@ =SUMIF($B3 B32,\"*\",D3:D32) D33 =SUMIF($B3 B32,\"*\",D3:D32) D"}
{"question": "1~13 16: OS 11 1~13 . . =SUM(IF(DAY() ctrl shift enter =SUM(IF(DAY() ctrl shift enter 2 @     2 . TOP 1 / ... and IrOnWaRe foresth2u kimjin**** ! 1 QR ? cynicalH . () ? 2 & 2 1~13 ! GIA () hesed**** Power Pivot u**** ! 16 16 . mk**** 123...941", "answer": "=SUM(IF(DAY() ctrl shift enter =SUM(IF(DAY() ctrl shift enter 2"}
{"question": "DATEDIF\n\nDATEDIF OS 10 DATEDIF . 0 1506 0 ? if( , 0, ..DateDif~) if( , 0, ..DateDif~) @ ! =if(ISBLANK(),0,DATEDIF()) . ! ! =if(ISBLANK(),0,DATEDIF()) . ! @ isblank ....... . =IF( V3= ,   isblank ....... . =IF( V3= ,   . TOP 3 / VBA . . juyoun**** name filter ? daniel () ? ? *** DATEDIF imagelookup , ? raw , kh**** . (len, replace) () .!! wl9**** & !! mmmmmmmuseong 033cola 5...941", "answer": "@ isblank ....... . =IF( V3= ,   isblank ....... . =IF( V3= ,"}
{"question": "(len, replace)\n\n, . , . > * > * > ** > ** KIMCHEOLSU > KIMCHE**** 2,3 1 * / 4,5 2 * / 6 4 * . 2,3,4,5 6 .. =IF(LEN(C2)>=6,REPLACE(C2,LEFT(C2,LEN(C2)-4),4,\"***\"),IF(LEN(C2)>=4,REPLACE(C2,LEN(C2)-1,2,\"**\"),REPLACE(C2,LEN(C2),1,\"*\"))) ​=IF(LEN(C2)>=6,REPLACE(C2,LEN(C2)-3,4,\"****\"),IF(LEN(C2)>=4,REPLACE(C2,LEN(C2)-1,2,\"**\"),REPLACE(C2,LEN(C2),1,\"*\")))", "answer": "=LET(n,LEN(A2),v,VLOOKUP(n,{2,1;4,2;6,4},2,1), IFERROR(LEFT(A2,n-v)&REPT(\"*\",v), )) . =LET(n,LEN(A2),v,VLOOKUP(n,{2,1;4,2;6,4},2,1), IFERROR(LEFT(A2,n-v)&REPT(\"*\",v), )) ."}
{"question": "& !! OS 11 & ( ) ?.. ( !) C2 =LET(MS, DATE(2025,A2,1), N, B2, ME, EOMONTH(MS,0), WE, MS+7*N-WEEKDAY(MS,2), WS, WE-6, IFS(MONTH(WS)=MONTH(WE),7,MONTH(WS) C2 =LET(MS, DATE(2025,A2,1), N, B2, ME, EOMONTH(MS,0), WE, MS+7*N-WEEKDAY(MS,2), WS, WE-6, IFS(MONTH(WS)=MONTH(WE),7,MONTH(WS) =LET( d, DATE(2025,5,1), w, WEEKNUM(SEQUENCE(DAY(EOMONTH(d,0)),,d),2), uData, UNIQUE(w), cnt, BYROW(uData, LAMBDA(r, SUM((w = r) * 1))), HSTACK(SEQUENCE(ROWS(uData)), cnt) ) =LET( d, DATE(2025,5,1), w, WEEKNUM(SEQUENCE(DAY(EOMONTH(d,0)),,d),2), uData, UNIQUE(w), cnt, BYROW(uData, LAMBDA(r, SUM((w = r) * 1))), HSTACK(SEQUENCE(ROWS(uData)), cnt) ) . @ Frequency . Frequency . @ .. .. ! ! . TOP 3 / VBA . . juyoun**** name filter ? daniel () ? ? *** DATEDIF imagelookup , ? raw , kh**** . (len, replace) () .!! wl9**** & !! mmmmmmmuseong 033cola 5...941", "answer": "C2 =LET(MS, DATE(2025,A2,1), N, B2, ME, EOMONTH(MS,0), WE, MS+7*N-WEEKDAY(MS,2), WS, WE-6, IFS(MONTH(WS)=MONTH(WE),7,MONTH(WS) C2 =LET(MS, DATE(2025,A2,1), N, B2, ME, EOMONTH(MS,0), WE, MS+7*N-WEEKDAY(MS,2), WS, WE-6, IFS(MONTH(WS)=MONTH(WE),7,MONTH(WS)"}
{"question": "VLOOKUP\n\nVLOOKUP OS 11 , VLOOKUP . , . . VLOOKUP-.xlsx (12 KB) Ctrl+Shift+Enter . C6 =IFERROR(VLOOKUP($B6, IF(D$14:D$20= ,  , CHOOSE({1,2}, $C$14 C$20,D$14:D$20)), 2, 0),  ) Ctrl+Shift+Enter . C6 =IFERROR(VLOOKUP($B6, IF(D$14:D$20= ,  , CHOOSE({1,2}, $C$14 C$20,D$14:D$20)), 2, 0),  ) @ b ) .  C6 =IFERROR(VLOOKUP($B6 ?*\", CHOOSE({1,2}, $C$15 C$20&D$15:D$20, D$15:D$20),2,0),   ) b ) .  C6 =IFERROR(VLOOKUP($B6 ?*\", CHOOSE({1,2}, $C$15 C$20&D$15:D$20, D$15:D$20),2,0),   ) !! , ? Ctrl+Shift+Enter ! !! , ? Ctrl+Shift+Enter ! . @ Ctrl+Shift+Enter . Ctrl+Shift+Enter . ~!! (_ _) ~!! (_ _) . TOP 4 / () hesed**** vlookup countifs ? Vlookup VLOOKUP !! ...!! Deoxone kojun**** 2 96m . GEEM ? 1 . lovese**** ( ) GEEM , + ? vba . . ...941", "answer": "Ctrl+Shift+Enter . C6 =IFERROR(VLOOKUP($B6, IF(D$14:D$20= ,  , CHOOSE({1,2}, $C$14 C$20,D$14:D$20)), 2, 0),  ) Ctrl+Shift+Enter . C6 =IFERROR(VLOOKUP($B6, IF(D$14:D$20= ,  , CHOOSE({1,2}, $C$14 C$20,D$14:D$20)), 2, 0),  )"}
{"question": "OS 11 , ! .xlsx (9 KB) =TRIM(TEXTSPLIT(A1,,\",\")) =TRIM(TEXTSPLIT(A1,,\",\")) @ !!!! !! !!!! !! . TOP 4 / () hesed**** vlookup countifs ? Vlookup VLOOKUP !! ...!! Deoxone kojun**** 2 96m . GEEM ? 1 . lovese**** ( ) GEEM , + ? vba . . ...941", "answer": "=TRIM(TEXTSPLIT(A1,,\",\")) =TRIM(TEXTSPLIT(A1,,\",\"))"}
{"question": ". endDate= .  C6  . 255 . CONCATENATE & ??", "answer": "=WEBSERVICE(SUBSTITUTE(A1,\"endDate=\",\"endDate= TEXT(TODAY(),\"mm/dd/yyyy\")) ) =WEBSERVICE(SUBSTITUTE(A1,\"endDate=\",\"endDate= TEXT(TODAY(),\"mm/dd/yyyy\")) )"}
{"question": "M365 OS 11 _.xlsx (10 KB) °º⁰ 3 . =LET(r,WRAPROWS(D9:O9,3), SUM((INDEX(r,,1)+INDEX(r,,2))*INDEX(r,,3))) __.xlsx (11 KB) 3 . =LET(r,WRAPROWS(D9:O9,3), SUM((INDEX(r,,1)+INDEX(r,,2))*INDEX(r,,3))) __.xlsx  º⁰ The One ~! !  ! . ~!! . ~! !  ! . ~!! . . . . TOP 6 / study**** ! COUNIF ? sumif? ? VBA ? groupby ? . SUMIF VBA ? HunnY _ Berea Sangwon Sangwon LUKE. (X,Y) ? . 1...45678...941", "answer": "°º⁰ 3 . =LET(r,WRAPROWS(D9:O9,3), SUM((INDEX(r,,1)+INDEX(r,,2))*INDEX(r,,3))) __.xlsx (11 KB) 3 . =LET(r,WRAPROWS(D9:O9,3), SUM((INDEX(r,,1)+INDEX(r,,2))*INDEX(r,,3))) __.xlsx"}
{"question": "! OS 11 1, 2 2 ! .xlsx (11 KB) =VLOOKUP(B26,B2:G20,IFERROR(MATCH(C26,B2:G2,1),2)) =VLOOKUP(B26,B2:G20,IFERROR(MATCH(C26,B2:G2,1),2)) @ ! ! °º⁰ index/match ~ =INDEX(C3:G20, MATCH(B26,B3:B20,1), MATCH(C26,C2:G2,1)) index/match ~ =INDEX(C3:G20, MATCH(B26,B3:B20,1), MATCH(C26,C2:G2,1))  º⁰ ! ! . TOP 7 / hoju**** hoju**** ! Hazys ( ) VBA Ctrl kok0**** / . sos pshf**** . . y**** coldback .. daswq . VLOOKUP 1...56789...941", "answer": "°º⁰ index/match ~ =INDEX(C3:G20, MATCH(B26,B3:B20,1), MATCH(C26,C2:G2,1)) index/match ~ =INDEX(C3:G20, MATCH(B26,B3:B20,1), MATCH(C26,C2:G2,1))"}
{"question": "TEXTJOIN(CHAR(10),TRUE,IF(_=C5,INDEX(_1._,,5), )) , .. ..", "answer": "=TEXTJOIN(CHAR(10),TRUE, UNIQUE(IF(_=C5,INDEX(_1._,,5), ))) UNIQUE.. =TEXTJOIN(CHAR(10),TRUE, UNIQUE(IF(_=C5,INDEX(_1._,,5), ))) UNIQUE.."}
{"question": "INDEX MATCH .\n\n. INDEX MATCH ... .. 6 10 6 9 .. ..", "answer": "=IFERROR( CHOOSE(COLUMNS($C$2:C$2), VLOOKUP($A3 + IF($B3= , 0, -1), $G I, IF($B3= , 3, 2), 0), VLOOKUP($A3 + IF($B3= , 0, 0), $G I, IF(C$2=\" \", IF($B3= , 2, 3), IF($B3= , 3, 2)), 0), VLOOKUP($A3 + IF($B3= , 1, 0), $G I, IF($B3= , 3, 2), 0) ),  ) =IFERROR( CHOOSE(COLUMNS($C$2:C$2), VLOOKUP($A3 + IF($B3= , 0, -1), $G I, IF($B3= , 3, 2), 0), VLOOKUP($A3 + IF($B3= , 0, 0), $G I, IF(C$2=\" \", IF($B3= , 2, 3), IF($B3= , 3, 2)), 0), VLOOKUP($A3 + IF($B3= , 1, 0), $G I, IF($B3= , 3, 2), 0) ),  )"}
{"question": "0 ? M365 OS 10 0 ? 0 SUBTOTAL ? 01.xlsm (21 KB) O7 =IF(AND(COUNTA($J$7 J$15)0),N7,0) O7 =IF(AND(COUNTA($J$7 J$15)0),N7,0) @     . TOP 9 / 0 , ? dncj**** MAX . (Shift+Spacebar), . 4 ? ? ? sjwhej12.com n 1 0 ? 2 !!!!! naver_5f055a605ee7d . 1 2 / 1......941", "answer": "O7 =IF(AND(COUNTA($J$7 J$15)0),N7,0) O7 =IF(AND(COUNTA($J$7 J$15)0),N7,0)"}
{"question": "M365 OS @ 463 5 52 152 0 _ 463 5 52 152 0 _ @ 151~350 1~199 0 ?? ... 199 0..... 200 350 .... 151 ?? =IF(A1 151~350 1~199 0 ?? ... 199 0..... 200 350 .... 151 ?? =IF(A1 0, 1000*MAX(0,MIN(A1-150, 350-150)) + 1500*MAX(0,A1-350)) @     . TOP 9 / 0 , ? dncj**** MAX . (Shift+Spacebar), . 4 ? ? ? sjwhej12.com n 1 0 ? 2 !!!!! naver_5f055a605ee7d . 1 2 / 1......941", "answer": "@ 151~350 1~199 0 ?? ... 199 0..... 200 350 .... 151 ?? =IF(A1 151~350 1~199 0 ?? ... 199 0..... 200 350 .... 151 ?? =IF(A1 0, 1000*MAX(0,MIN(A1-150, 350-150)) + 1500*MAX(0,A1-350))"}
{"question": "!! OS 11 . 1 . 2 1 . 1000 !! =UNIQUE(1) =VLOOKUP(2#,1,2,0) =UNIQUE(1) =VLOOKUP(2#,1,2,0) @ ! vlookup ? ! vlookup ? ... -- .. ID .. ... -- .. ID .. . TOP 10 / . rmlik**** + . naver_5f055a605ee7d VLOOKUP #VALUE! . hesed**** , 8, 0 0 ? Suu !! ~ 1......941", "answer": "=UNIQUE(1) =VLOOKUP(2#,1,2,0) =UNIQUE(1) =VLOOKUP(2#,1,2,0)"}
{"question": "#SPILL! IN NO C2501 HMM LE HAVRE . IN NO =INDEX(!K:K,MATCH(' PL'!U6:W6,!G:G)) 22 . B23:K76 .", "answer": "=INDEX(!K:K,MATCH(' PL'!U6,!G:G)) =INDEX(!K:K,MATCH(' PL'!U6,!G:G))"}
{"question": ". . ①(A~C) , , . ② (D~H) (D~H) . : =IF(AND()), , \"X\") ③(I~J) : D~H . 5 20 .(D AA ) , .", "answer": "@** =SUMIFS(A:A,B:B,\"= I3)+SUMIFS(A:A,B:B,\"= I3)+SUMIFS(A:A,B:B, = I3,C:C, ) J3"}
{"question": "() ? M365 OS 11 test.xlsx (16 KB) C , C ..~ C2=IF(COUNTIF($E$3 E$32,$A$3 A$105),\"Expense\",\"Not Expense\") . C , C ..~ C2=IF(COUNTIF($E$3 E$32,$A$3 A$105),\"Expense\",\"Not Expense\") . @ !! :) !! :) . TOP 13 / () ? spill ta**** -.__.- , vlookup index&match ! plzz , 2 ysd**** API slrspa fae**** ~! J . sumifs SeulGi # 1...15...941", "answer": "C , C ..~ C2=IF(COUNTIF($E$3 E$32,$A$3 A$105),\"Expense\",\"Not Expense\") . C , C ..~ C2=IF(COUNTIF($E$3 E$32,$A$3 A$105),\"Expense\",\"Not Expense\") ."}
{"question": "~! J OS 10 ~! . . ~! ~! =CHOOSE(MIN(VLOOKUP(J3:O3,$G$2 H$6,2,0)),\"e\",\"d\",\"c\",\"b\",\"a\") =CHOOSE(MIN(VLOOKUP(J3:O3,$G$2 H$6,2,0)),\"e\",\"d\",\"c\",\"b\",\"a\") °º⁰ =CHAR(MAX(CODE(A1:F1))) ctrl+shift+enter . =CHAR(MAX(CODE(A1:F1))) ctrl+shift+enter . . TOP 13 / () ? spill ta**** -.__.- , vlookup index&match ! plzz , 2 ysd**** API slrspa fae**** ~! J . sumifs SeulGi # 1...15...941", "answer": "°º⁰ =CHAR(MAX(CODE(A1:F1))) ctrl+shift+enter . =CHAR(MAX(CODE(A1:F1))) ctrl+shift+enter ."}
{"question": "sumifs\n\n=SUMIFS(H:H,E:E, = EOMONTH(DATE(2025,1,1),B6-2)+1,E:E, EOMONTH(DATE(2025,1,1),B6-1)+1)   ?? .", "answer": "=SUMIFS(H:H,E:E, = EOMONTH(DATE(2025,1,1),B6-2)+1,E:E, ) =SUMIFS(H:H,E:E, = EOMONTH(DATE(2025,1,1),B6-2)+1,E:E,\"K:K,  )"}
{"question": ".. SUMPRODUCT INDEX & MATCH, OFFSET 2 1,2,3 !", "answer": "=SUMIFS(D:D, A:A,I2, B:B,J2, C:C,K2) =SUMIFS(D:D, A:A,I2, B:B,J2, C:C,K2)"}
{"question": "/ M365 OS 11 ? .xlsx (10 KB) =IF( COUNTIF($D$1 D1, D2)=0,  ,  ) =IF( COUNTIF($D$1 D1, D2)=0,  ,  ) @ . TOP 14 / (hwp) . ...   ak (41 ) / . ? ? RaeJong .. sj !! mmm / ? . ? !.. ! . SJ 1...16...941", "answer": "=IF( COUNTIF($D$1 D1, D2)=0,  ,  ) =IF( COUNTIF($D$1 D1, D2)=0,  ,  )"}
{"question": "M365 OS 11 .. _.xlsx (13 KB) ... =LET(D,B3, S, SEQUENCE(LEN(D)), DC, UPPER(MID(D,S,1)), A, SEQUENCE(26), AL, CHAR(A+64), DV, XLOOKUP(DC, AL, A), V, \"AEIOU\", DN, N(IFERROR(FIND(DC,V),0)>0), DT, TEXTJOIN(,,IF(DN,DN,\" \")), DX, BYROW(S, LAMBDA(r, LEN(TEXTAFTER(LEFT(DT,r),\" \",-1,,1)))), dxt, TEXTJOIN(,,DX), DY, BYROW(S, LAMBDA(r, IFERROR(RIGHT(TEXTBEFORE(RIGHT(dxt,LEN(D)-r+1),\"0\",,,1),1)*1,0))), SUMPRODUCT(DV,DY+1)) ... =LET(D,B3, S, SEQUENCE(LEN(D)), DC, UPPER(MID(D,S,1)), A, SEQUENCE(26), AL, CHAR(A+64), DV, XLOOKUP(DC, AL, A), V, \"AEIOU\", DN, N(IFERROR(FIND(DC,V),0)>0), DT, TEXTJOIN(,,IF(DN,DN,\" \")), DX, BYROW(S, LAMBDA(r, LEN(TEXTAFTER(LEFT(DT,r),\" \",-1,,1)))), dxt, TEXTJOIN(,,DX), DY, BYROW(S, LAMBDA(r, IFERROR(RIGHT(TEXTBEFORE(RIGHT(dxt,LEN(D)-r+1),\"0\",,,1),1)*1,0))), SUMPRODUCT(DV,DY+1)) =LET(t,UPPER(B3),s,MID(t,SEQUENCE(LEN(t)),1), n,CODE(s)-64,isvowel,LAMBDA(v,N(ISNUMBER(SEARCH(s,\"AEIOU\")))), rsort,LAMBDA(r,SORTBY(r,SEQUENCE(LEN(t)),-1)), i,isvowel(s),ii,SCAN(0,i,LAMBDA(a,b,IF(b=1,a+b,0))),ir,rsort(ii), lr,SCAN(0,ir,LAMBDA(a,b,IF(b=0,1,IF(b=LET(t,UPPER(B3),s,MID(t,SEQUENCE(LEN(t)),1), n,CODE(s)-64,isvowel,LAMBDA(v,N(ISNUMBER(SEARCH(s,\"AEIOU\")))), rsort,LAMBDA(r,SORTBY(r,SEQUENCE(LEN(t)),-1)), i,isvowel(s),ii,SCAN(0,i,LAMBDA(a,b,IF(b=1,a+b,0))),ir,rsort(ii), lr,SCAN(0,ir,LAMBDA(a,b,IF(b=0,1,IF(b !! @ ? ? @ ! Q&A ~ ! Q&A ~ .. ...T.T ??..2~3 .. ..@.@ .... ..  .. ...T.T ??..2~3 .. ..@.@ .... ..  @ SCAN . =LET(D,B3, S,SEQUENCE(LEN(D)), DC,UPPER(MID(D,S,1)), A,SEQUENCE(26), DV,XLOOKUP(DC,CHAR(A+64), A), DN,N(IFERROR(FIND(DC,\"AEIOU\"),0)>0), DX,BYROW(S, LAMBDA(r, LEN(TEXTBEFORE(MID(TEXTJOIN(,,IF(DN,DN,\" \")),r,LEN(D)),\" \",,,1)))), DY,SCAN(,DX, LAMBDA(b,c, IFS(c=0,0,b>0,b,TRUE,c))), SUMPRODUCT(DV,DY+1)) DN , DX ,,, 3,2,1 DY Scan . (ii) (ir) (lr) (ll). SCAN . =LET(D,B3, S,SEQUENCE(LEN(D)), DC,UPPER(MID(D,S,1)), A,SEQUENCE(26), DV,XLOOKUP(DC,CHAR(A+64), A), DN,N(IFERROR(FIND(DC,\"AEIOU\"),0)>0), DX,BYROW(S, LAMBDA(r, LEN(TEXTBEFORE(MID(TEXTJOIN(,,IF(DN,DN,\" \")),r,LEN(D)),\" \",,,1)))), DY,SCAN(,DX, LAMBDA(b,c, IFS(c=0,0,b>0,b,TRUE,c))), SUMPRODUCT(DV,DY+1)) DN , DX ,,, 3,2,1 DY Scan . (ii) (ir) (lr) (ll). @ ..... ..^...........  1 .. ..... ..^...........  1 .. =LET( txt, LOWER(B3), ch,MID(txt,SEQUENCE(LEN(txt)),1), , SUM(UNICODE(ch)-96), , TEXTSPLIT(CONCAT(IF(ISNUMBER(SEARCH(ch,\"aeiou\")),ch,\"/\")),\"/\",,TRUE), , IFERROR(SUM(REDUCE( , , LAMBDA(a,b, VSTACK(a, SUM(LEN(b) * (UNICODE(MID(b, SEQUENCE(LEN(b)), 1))-96) ))))),0), + ) =LET( txt, LOWER(B3), ch,MID(txt,SEQUENCE(LEN(txt)),1), , SUM(UNICODE(ch)-96), , REGEXEXTRACT(txt,\"+\",1), , IFERROR(SUM(REDUCE( , , LAMBDA(a,b, VSTACK(a, SUM(LEN(b) * (UNICODE(MID(b, SEQUENCE(LEN(b)), 1))-96) ))))),0), +) =LET( txt, LOWER(B3), ch,MID(txt,SEQUENCE(LEN(txt)),1), , SUM(UNICODE(ch)-96), , TEXTSPLIT(CONCAT(IF(ISNUMBER(SEARCH(ch,\"aeiou\")),ch,\"/\")),\"/\",,TRUE), , IFERROR(SUM(REDUCE( , , LAMBDA(a,b, VSTACK(a, SUM(LEN(b) * (UNICODE(MID(b, SEQUENCE(LEN(b)), 1))-96) ))))),0), + ) =LET( txt, LOWER(B3), ch,MID(txt,SEQUENCE(LEN(txt)),1), , SUM(UNICODE(ch)-96), , REGEXEXTRACT(txt,\"+\",1), , IFERROR(SUM(REDUCE( , , LAMBDA(a,b, VSTACK(a, SUM(LEN(b) * (UNICODE(MID(b, SEQUENCE(LEN(b)), 1))-96) ))))),0), +) @ . . =LET(x,LOWER(B3),c,REGEXEXTRACT(x,\"+\",1),SUM((CODE(MID(c,SEQUENCE(LEN(x)),1) )-96)*(LEN(c)+1),CODE(REGEXEXTRACT(x, ,1))-96)) =LET(x,LOWER(B3),c,REGEXEXTRACT(x,\"+\",1),SUM((CODE(MID(c,SEQUENCE(LEN(x)),1) )-96)*(LEN(c)+1),CODE(REGEXEXTRACT(x, ,1))-96)) @ . =LET(x,LOWER(B3),c,REGEXEXTRACT(x,\"+\",1), SUM((CODE(MID(c,SEQUENCE(LEN(x)),1) )-96)*(LEN(c)+1), CODE(REGEXEXTRACT(x, ,1))-96)) c . .. b^.^) . =LET(x,LOWER(B3),c,REGEXEXTRACT(x,\"+\",1), SUM((CODE(MID(c,SEQUENCE(LEN(x)),1) )-96)*(LEN(c)+1), CODE(REGEXEXTRACT(x, ,1))-96)) c . .. b^.^) . TOP 15 / ~ Miniseries.KR !! mmm . PowerBI Dax ?  ( ) 15- 1- SUMIFS , . .. SJ ? gh**** . VBA . !!.... ... khs**** ! 1...17...941", "answer": "=LET(x,LOWER(B3),c,REGEXEXTRACT(x,\"+\",1),SUM((CODE(MID(c,SEQUENCE(LEN(x)),1) )-96)*(LEN(c)+1),CODE(REGEXEXTRACT(x, ,1))-96)) =LET(x,LOWER(B3),c,REGEXEXTRACT(x,\"+\",1),SUM((CODE(MID(c,SEQUENCE(LEN(x)),1) )-96)*(LEN(c)+1),CODE(REGEXEXTRACT(x, ,1))-96))"}
{"question": ". . 2019 , =IFERROR(INDEX(!$A$2 V$93, SMALL(IF(ISNUMBER(SEARCH(!$A$1,!$A$2 B$93)),MATCH(ROW(!$A$2 B$93), ROW(!$A$2 B$93)),  ), ROWS($A$1:A1)), COLUMNS($A$1:A1)), ) , 2 ..? .... !!!", "answer": ".. A4=IFERROR(INDEX(, SMALL(IF(ISNUMBER(SEARCH(!$A$1,:])),ROW(:])-1),ROWS($B$1 B1)), COLUMNS($A$1:A1)), ) ctrl+shift+enter .. A4=IFERROR(INDEX(, SMALL(IF(ISNUMBER(SEARCH(!$A$1,:])),ROW(:])-1),ROWS($B$1 B1)), COLUMNS($A$1:A1)), ) ctrl+shift+enter"}
{"question": "1 a 3 =iferror(index(Sheet1!$A A,small(if(Sheet1!$A A=\"A\",row(Sheet1!$A A)-row(Sheet1!A$1)+1,row(1:1))), )", "answer": "B1 , . , . A3 =IFERROR( INDEX(Sheet1!A:A, 1/AGGREGATE(14,6, (Sheet1!$A$2 A$100=$B$1)/ROW(Sheet1!$A$2 A$100), ROW(A1) )),  ) B1 , . , . A3 =IFERROR( INDEX(Sheet1!A:A, 1/AGGREGATE(14,6, (Sheet1!$A$2 A$100=$B$1)/ROW(Sheet1!$A$2 A$100), ROW(A1) )),  )"}
{"question": ". . .. A B M N O ~ 1, 2, 1, = A1 / $A$1 = B1 / $A$1 =M1 / $A$1 2, 1, 13 . () . ~ (13) . 25 5 , A 2,4,6,8 245 . A B M N O ~ 1, 2, 1, 2, = A1 / $A$1 = B1 / $B$1 =M1 / $B$1 =N1 / $B$1 2, 1, 2,4,6,7,,, 13 . ..?", "answer": "1 , . , , Today . A1 =Today() , .xlsx (10 KB) 1 , . , , Today . A1 =Today() , .xlsx"}
{"question": "=LOOKUP(2,1/(COUNTIF($I$1:I1,$G$2 G$23)=0),$G$2:G23 ) (, .", "answer": "=LET(Data,G2:G37,,UNIQUE(FILTER(Data,Data )), SORT(CHOOSE({1,2},,COUNTIF(Data,)),2)) =LET(Data,G2:G37,,UNIQUE(FILTER(Data,Data )), SORT(CHOOSE({1,2},,COUNTIF(Data,)),2))"}
{"question": "(Derek) OS 11 ? ( 1500 ) .xlsx (10 KB) =SORTBY(C4:G10, VLOOKUP(C4:C10, { ,1 ,2 ,3} ,2,0),,F4:F10,) (;) , . =SORTBY(C4:G10, VLOOKUP(C4:C10, { ,1 ,2 ,3} ,2,0),,F4:F10,) (;) , . (Derek) @ . , ? 15 20 . . , ? 15 20 . @(Derek) VLOOKUP IFERROR(Match(C4:C10, P1:P15, 0),99) VLOOKUP IFERROR(Match(C4:C10, P1:P15, 0),99) (Derek) @ . . . . . . TOP 16 / _ ! ! mmm (Derek) (Derek) LIVE 219 - ' ' . AURIC 25x25 ? . . . , ! min . .. . !! ~ 1...18...941", "answer": "=SORTBY(C4:G10, VLOOKUP(C4:C10, { ,1 ,2 ,3} ,2,0),,F4:F10,) (;) , . =SORTBY(C4:G10, VLOOKUP(C4:C10, { ,1 ,2 ,3} ,2,0),,F4:F10,) (;) , ."}
{"question": "+1, -1 .\n\n. =1, =-1 ? =IF(C3= ,\"1\") . .", "answer": "°º⁰ . . =COUNTIF(C3:G3, )-COUNTIF(C3:G3, ) =SUMPRODUCT((C3:G3= )-(C3:G3= )) =SUM(IF(C3:G3= ,1,IF(C3:G3= ,-1,0))) . . =COUNTIF(C3:G3, )-COUNTIF(C3:G3, ) =SUMPRODUCT((C3:G3= )-(C3:G3= )) =SUM(IF(C3:G3= ,1,IF(C3:G3= ,-1,0)))"}
{"question": "() OS 11 , °º⁰ (B,E ) =WEEKDAY(D2,2)=6 =WEEKDAY(D2,2)=7 _--.xlsx (10 KB) (B,E ) =WEEKDAY(D2,2)=6 =WEEKDAY(D2,2)=7 _--.xlsx     . . . . . TOP 17 / ~ . chloe .. +1, -1 . vba chl000**** killerg**** VBA kok0**** nanjose**** yon**** Ctrl+E E () VB ' ? GEEM Sales Dashboard () lee index match 1...19...941", "answer": "°º⁰ (B,E ) =WEEKDAY(D2,2)=6 =WEEKDAY(D2,2)=7 _--.xlsx (10 KB) (B,E ) =WEEKDAY(D2,2)=6 =WEEKDAY(D2,2)=7 _--.xlsx"}
{"question": "index match\n\nindex match OS 11 ? ? °º⁰ find . =INDEX($C$2 C$7, MATCH(TRUE, ISNUMBER(FIND(E3,$B$2 B$7)),0)) find . =INDEX($C$2 C$7, MATCH(TRUE, ISNUMBER(FIND(E3,$B$2 B$7)),0))  º⁰ . . =VLOOKUP(\"* e3 *\", b2:c7,2,0) =VLOOKUP(\"* e3 *\", b2:c7,2,0) @ . TOP 17 / ~ . chloe .. +1, -1 . vba chl000**** killerg**** VBA kok0**** nanjose**** yon**** Ctrl+E E () VB ' ? GEEM Sales Dashboard () lee index match 1...19...941", "answer": "°º⁰ find . =INDEX($C$2 C$7, MATCH(TRUE, ISNUMBER(FIND(E3,$B$2 B$7)),0)) find . =INDEX($C$2 C$7, MATCH(TRUE, ISNUMBER(FIND(E3,$B$2 B$7)),0))"}
{"question": "6 ? OS 11 - - D4 =DATEDIF(DATE((--LEFT(D4,2)<MOD(YEAR(TODAY()),100)+20)+19&LEFT(D4,2),MID(D4,3,2),RIGHT(D4,2)),TODAY(),\"y\") D4 DATEDIF D4 =DATEDIF(DATE((--LEFT(D4,2)<MOD(YEAR(TODAY()),100)+20)+19&LEFT(D4,2),MID(D4,3,2),RIGHT(D4,2)),TODAY(),\"y\") D4 DATEDIF @ ? ? @ ! ! @ -2 -3 . -2 -3 . @ 20 30 40 20 30 40 . @ int(/10) 0\" =int(DATEDIF(DATE((--LEFT(D4,2)<MOD(YEAR(TODAY()),100)+20)+19&LEFT(D4,2),MID(D4,3,2),RIGHT(D4,2)),TODAY(),\"y\")/10) 0\" int(/10) 0\" =int(DATEDIF(DATE((--LEFT(D4,2)<MOD(YEAR(TODAY()),100)+20)+19&LEFT(D4,2),MID(D4,3,2),RIGHT(D4,2)),TODAY(),\"y\")/10) 0\"     . TOP 18 / ) .. 10.0 ? IF . neoburi 6 ? INDEX + MATCH ! Aberdeen / Range Insert . jihye**** , ? MICROSOFT 365 : . nams 1...20...941", "answer": "D4 =DATEDIF(DATE((--LEFT(D4,2)<MOD(YEAR(TODAY()),100)+20)+19&LEFT(D4,2),MID(D4,3,2),RIGHT(D4,2)),TODAY(),\"y\") D4 DATEDIF D4 =DATEDIF(DATE((--LEFT(D4,2)<MOD(YEAR(TODAY()),100)+20)+19&LEFT(D4,2),MID(D4,3,2),RIGHT(D4,2)),TODAY(),\"y\") D4 DATEDIF"}
{"question": "OS 11 BOT TOP ? . test.xls (30 KB) countifs . C4=SUMPRODUCT(ROW($A$1 A$1001)*(TOP!$A$1 A$1001=A4)*(TOP!$B$1 B$1001=B4)) TOP ROW() C4=COUNTIFS(TOP!A:A,A4,TOP!B:B,B4) . countifs . C4=SUMPRODUCT(ROW($A$1 A$1001)*(TOP!$A$1 A$1001=A4)*(TOP!$B$1 B$1001=B4)) TOP ROW() C4=COUNTIFS(TOP!A:A,A4,TOP!B:B,B4) . . TOP 18 / ) .. 10.0 ? IF . neoburi 6 ? INDEX + MATCH ! Aberdeen / Range Insert . jihye**** , ? MICROSOFT 365 : . nams 1...20...941", "answer": "countifs . C4=SUMPRODUCT(ROW($A$1 A$1001)*(TOP!$A$1 A$1001=A4)*(TOP!$B$1 B$1001=B4)) TOP ROW() C4=COUNTIFS(TOP!A:A,A4,TOP!B:B,B4) . countifs . C4=SUMPRODUCT(ROW($A$1 A$1001)*(TOP!$A$1 A$1001=A4)*(TOP!$B$1 B$1001=B4)) TOP ROW() C4=COUNTIFS(TOP!A:A,A4,TOP!B:B,B4) ."}
{"question": "2 countif\n\n2 countif M365 OS countfis(e:e,d2:d6) countfis(e:e,d2:d6) @ ! ! . °º⁰ I2 =COUNTIF(E2:E6,D2:D6) G2 =COUNTIF($E$2 E$6,D2) I2 =COUNTIF(E2:E6,D2:D6) G2 =COUNTIF($E$2 E$6,D2)  º⁰ ! ! ... . ... . @ =HSTACK(A2:A6,B2:B6) 2 . take(,,1) take(,,-1) take(,,1) take(,,-1) . =HSTACK(A2:A6,B2:B6) 2 . take(,,1) take(,,-1) take(,,1) take(,,-1) . @ =LET(Data,HSTACK(A2:A6,B2:B6),BYROW(TAKE(Data,,1),LAMBDA(r,SUM((TAKE(Data,,-1)=r)*1)))) =LET(Data,HSTACK(A2:A6,B2:B6),BYROW(TAKE(Data,,1),LAMBDA(r,SUM((TAKE(Data,,-1)=r)*1)))) @ ! ! . TOP 19 / 2 countif . VBA shhhha . mmm ... ( ) LIVE 196 - _ , . SUM IFERROR Excel eagle N On Error Resume Next ? GEEM index hossang**** () TOP10 0 ( ) peac**** ! Aberdeen 1...21...941", "answer": "@ =LET(Data,HSTACK(A2:A6,B2:B6),BYROW(TAKE(Data,,1),LAMBDA(r,SUM((TAKE(Data,,-1)=r)*1)))) =LET(Data,HSTACK(A2:A6,B2:B6),BYROW(TAKE(Data,,1),LAMBDA(r,SUM((TAKE(Data,,-1)=r)*1))))"}
{"question": "OS 11 . 2025-03.xlsx (248 KB) ... .. . 2025-03.xlsx (297 KB) ... .. . 2025-03.xlsx @ , , @ . . ,, . ....... ,, . ....... : data =TRIMRANGE(!$A AC) ==> : A2 =Rawdata!A2:A1015*1 ==> A2 L2:T2 H2 =IFERROR(Rawdata!H2:H1015*1, ) I2 =IFERROR(Rawdata!I2:I1015*1, ) --2025-03.xlsx (301 KB) : data =TRIMRANGE(!$A AC) ==> : A2 =Rawdata!A2:A1015*1 ==> A2 L2:T2 H2 =IFERROR(Rawdata!H2:H1015*1, ) I2 =IFERROR(Rawdata!I2:I1015*1, ) --2025-03.xlsx . . .... . . .... 4 ? . 4 ? . @ 4 Rawdata . 4 (1234) A2 =Rawdata!A2:A1234*1 --> *1 . 4 Rawdata . 4 (1234) A2 =Rawdata!A2:A1234*1 --> *1 . .. ? .. ? @ ... . email layout . excel . ... . email layout . excel . @ . . @ . ..... . . . ..... . . . TOP 19 / 2 countif . VBA shhhha . mmm ... ( ) LIVE 196 - _ , . SUM IFERROR Excel eagle N On Error Resume Next ? GEEM index hossang**** () TOP10 0 ( ) peac**** ! Aberdeen 1...21...941", "answer": ": data =TRIMRANGE(!$A AC) ==> : A2 =Rawdata!A2:A1015*1 ==> A2 L2:T2 H2 =IFERROR(Rawdata!H2:H1015*1, ) I2 =IFERROR(Rawdata!I2:I1015*1, ) --2025-03.xlsx (301 KB) : data =TRIMRANGE(!$A AC) ==> : A2 =Rawdata!A2:A1015*1 ==> A2 L2:T2 H2 =IFERROR(Rawdata!H2:H1015*1, ) I2 =IFERROR(Rawdata!I2:I1015*1, ) --2025-03.xlsx"}
{"question": ". mmm1010 OS 11 . , . Leejch914 ... ... =IF( COUNT(SEARCH({ , },A1)),  , ) =IF( COUNT(SEARCH({ , },A1)),  , ) mmm1010 !!!!! !!!!! . TOP 19 / 2 countif . VBA shhhha . mmm ... ( ) LIVE 196 - _ , . SUM IFERROR Excel eagle N On Error Resume Next ? GEEM index hossang**** () TOP10 0 ( ) peac**** ! Aberdeen 1...21...941", "answer": "=IF( COUNT(SEARCH({ , },A1)),  , ) =IF( COUNT(SEARCH({ , },A1)),  , )"}
{"question": "N . 3 4 J8 (COUNTIFS(OFFSET($B$1,,,ROW($B$1 B$100)),I8)=H8) LOOKUP N ?? ( ) N XLOOKUP,FLTER, SUMPRODUCT N . ROWIFS 2021 N XLOOKUP FILTER . 3 . sumproduct LARGE LOOKUP IF LARGE . 2021 . 2021", "answer": "Offset( ) =IFERROR(TEXTJOIN(\"_\",1,INDEX(FILTER($C$5 F$14,$B$5 B$14=$I8),$H8,)), ) Offset( ) =IFERROR(TEXTJOIN(\"_\",1,INDEX(FILTER($C$5 F$14,$B$5 B$14=$I8),$H8,)), )"}
{"question": "15 1 ..\n\n15 1 .. sj M365 OS 11 ! 15 1 .. 15--.xlsx (31 KB) °º⁰ ~ 4 . . J2 =SUMPRODUCT(($A$2 A$380=$I2)*(HOUR($B$2 B$380-TIME(0,15,0))=J$1)*$C$2 C$380) _15.xlsx (43 KB) ~ 4 . . J2 =SUMPRODUCT(($A$2 A$380=$I2)*(HOUR($B$2 B$380-TIME(0,15,0))=J$1)*$C$2 C$380) _15.xlsx sj  º⁰ ! . ! . . . _15.xlsx (45 KB) . _15.xlsx . TOP 20 / . sumproduct , S VLOOKUP ? emma . GPT 15 1 .. sj VBA 2, Babelfish CVS . ? ! mmm . kurapara - 2 . 1...22...941", "answer": "°º⁰ ~ 4 . . J2 =SUMPRODUCT(($A$2 A$380=$I2)*(HOUR($B$2 B$380-TIME(0,15,0))=J$1)*$C$2 C$380) _15.xlsx (43 KB) ~ 4 . . J2 =SUMPRODUCT(($A$2 A$380=$I2)*(HOUR($B$2 B$380-TIME(0,15,0))=J$1)*$C$2 C$380) _15.xlsx"}
{"question": ". kurapara OS 11 B2:F2 + + + ?? . . -.xlsx (10 KB) =OR(COUNTIF($B$2 F$2,\"* B$5 B$9 *\")*COUNTIF(B2,\"* B$5 B$9 *\")>=2) COUNTIF , COUNTIF 2 .. 1 OR() =OR(COUNTIF($B$2 F$2,\"* B$5 B$9 *\")*COUNTIF(B2,\"* B$5 B$9 *\")>=2) COUNTIF , COUNTIF 2 .. 1 OR() kurapara @ OR OR ctrl+shift+enter. ctrl+shift+enter. . TOP 20 / . sumproduct , S VLOOKUP ? emma . GPT 15 1 .. sj VBA 2, Babelfish CVS . ? ! mmm . kurapara - 2 . 1...22...941", "answer": "=OR(COUNTIF($B$2 F$2,\"* B$5 B$9 *\")*COUNTIF(B2,\"* B$5 B$9 *\")>=2) COUNTIF , COUNTIF 2 .. 1 OR() =OR(COUNTIF($B$2 F$2,\"* B$5 B$9 *\")*COUNTIF(B2,\"* B$5 B$9 *\")>=2) COUNTIF , COUNTIF 2 .. 1 OR()"}
{"question": ".. OS 11 18 13 12 11 ... ... .xlsx (20 KB) =SUMPRODUCT(SUBSTITUTE(SUBSTITUTE(1,:],\"(\", ),\"ea)\", )*1:])+ =SUMPRODUCT(SUBSTITUTE(SUBSTITUTE(1,:],\"(\", ),\"ea)\", )*1:])+ . . TOP 21 / 5 VBA ? X -> 1 . glfksh . as 6 RAWDATA PDF .. . , 10 ,, Filter 1...23...941", "answer": "=SUMPRODUCT(SUBSTITUTE(SUBSTITUTE(1,:],\"(\", ),\"ea)\", )*1:])+ =SUMPRODUCT(SUBSTITUTE(SUBSTITUTE(1,:],\"(\", ),\"ea)\", )*1:])+"}
